This song has become incredibly popular among young people in China.
The tongue pain repeated in the lyrics is a Chinese word meaning to live flat.
The expression is now used to describe someone with no interest in buying a home, marrying,
working more than necessary to get by.
Line flat gained recognition among the younger generation, largely because of fatigue and
disappointment from social competition.
I can't do it like that.
I don't have any strength.
I'm not a good person.
I'm a good person.
I don't have to buy it.
It's too big.
So, what is it?
It's hard to see people for a long time.
As the economic development of China continues, young people are wondering what they get
out of their efforts.
In this episode, we lend an ear to those who've chosen to lie flat.
This farming village is located in Hubei Province, in northern China.
Here, one man has made the conscious choice to lie flat.
Sun Lin-Nin is 35 years old.
Four years ago, he quit his job and assigned it to devote most of his time to gaming.
It's okay to go out at afternoon, six or six.
My activities are very good.
Because I don't use the main body of the work.
I don't have the main body for the whole day.
I have to go to the office for a day,
I have to eat for a day,
I have to eat for a day.
You can see that my wife knows that.
I spent 15 years in China.
Soon, it's just one of many young people across China who prefer lying flat.
It all began from a post on the internet in April of 2021.
Lying flat is justice.
What could be wrong with just taking it easy?
I'm very restrained by competition and traditional values
and are consumed by stress every day.
I'm sick of wearing myself out,
working toward a traditional family.
I want to seek out a simple life.
Now that I've chosen to life flat,
I have nothing to fear.
The post was the spark, the litophyre.
The post was the spark that lit a fire, spreading lying flat across the nation.
It came to represent an unmotivated, unambitious lifestyle not bound by conventional values.
One aspect of lying flat is to not buy a home.
Real estate prices have risen drastically in China, growing fivefold in the past 20 years.
To young members of the workforce, home ownership is becoming an increasingly unentainable dream.
Another point is remaining single.
Since home ownership is largely viewed as a prerequisite for men to marry in China,
LineFlat means giving up on tying the knot.
As the lifestyle continues its growth as a social phenomenon, there was even an online community
founded for those who share the world view, with nearly 200,000 members.
At my current salary, I wouldn't be able to buy a home until I'm 80.
What a joke!
I'd rather live flat.
Today was my 100th day of lying flat.
I've kept to a modest lifestyle of non-consumption and solitude.
Now there's even merchandise that promotes the movement.
Whether through smartphone cases or t-shirts, lying flat shows no signs of slowing down.
Stephen continues his laid back policy while residing at his parents' house.
He lives with his 70-year-old father, who suffered a cerebral hemorrhage last year.
Soon lost his mother to illness at a young age, leaving his father to raise him alone.
So, what's your favorite food?
I don't know what to eat.
I want to eat something like chicken.
I eat something like chicken.
I don't eat chicken with rice.
I don't eat rice with rice.
I think it's more delicious than what I eat.
Did you have any ideas about the future?
I have never been to the old school.
I have never thought about it.
I was in the middle of the war.
Yesterday, when we were talking about the past,
I asked if there was any ideas about the future.
I was wondering,
what is the future?
I was thinking about the future.
I was not interested in the future.
Soon had once set his sights on getting married.
To provide a decent life, he began an intensely busy job at a welding factory when he was
20.
The next day, it was not as good as the last one.
That's right.
The light of the TV, you can't take your skin off.
Once you take your skin off, take one, take it off.
The next day, you have to take your own skin off.
The next day, there was a car accident.
Two cents.
It was quite a lot.
The money was for the money, right?
So, it was not full of money.
Soon continued working diligently, saving up for the day when he could find a bride.
But when he was 28, the factory ran into financial woes.
Soon's earnings were halved, and he began to wonder how he could make a living.
specially for fighters for soldiers,
and also for tanks that are selected,
and to get along with him for fights.
Because I was visiting a big house
on my Summer twenties,
that is where I came from,
where my family kicked me,
he was the last to shoot.
He was getting ready for internacional timing in 2015,
he will go throughout the year
till the summer that he took place.
And on his way with thoseATGs.
We told him that his distance in their revolving style
is just way better for him.
In the farming region where soon lives, he's one of many young men who share these concerns.
So, it's just...
It's just...
It's just something special.
I have some good people here.
I grew up better than I was.
I have a car, a house, and a car.
But I can't find a car.
I just didn't see it.
I was too young.
Yes, too young.
Starting in 1978,
The Chinese government enforced the one child policy.
For farming villages, its legacy meant new obstacles to marriage.
Due to the emphasis on labor and succession,
many families in the regions hoped for a son.
Since they could have only a single child,
some families chose abortion if they discovered they carried a girl.
The births of boys far outnumbered girls.
And a generation later, the number of men between age 20 and 40,
now exceeds women by 17 million.
Many residents of the villages
travel to cities in order to work and eventually marry.
But having to take care of his father,
it was hard for soon to leave the village entirely.
After I met my son, I found out that he was a man who was a master of the business.
After I met him, I found out that he was a master of the business.
Soon has given up entirely on ever-managing to marry within his village.
Having been singled out as a good for nothing by other residents,
who insist he should work and get married. Soon leads a secluded life.
Leo Mantau is a writer and commentator.
He's analyzed that the trend of young people lying flat
is deeply rooted in the structure of Chinese society.
In China and many other countries,
they've been compared to other countries.
Many people are able to meet the problem of life.
For example, they are married.
For example, they are young.
These problems are not a very suitable society-based solution.
These questions need to be answered by their own questions.
They have no choice but to solve the problem of the end of the question.
This is a very big question.
The second question is,
The way the young people in China are growing,
the way they are growing,
But the media of the Communist Party has made its own views clear as well.
As our country pursues economic growth, it grapples with aging and a declining birth
rate.
We must be cautious of lying flat.
Lying flat is not justice.
It is shameful.
China is filled with new opportunities.
Those who persevere can attain success.
A life of perseverance is a happy life.
Just a few days after this statement was published, the line-flat online community was closed.
T-shirts and other related goods were delisted from websites.
The strict censorship drew cries of protest from those committed to the lifestyle.
Lin Shaolin documents his days spent lying flat on social media as he lives in the city.
Among skyrocketing housing prices, Lin has given up on ever owning a home.
One day, he visits an affluent residential neighborhood.
If you go to the market, it's a high-quality city.
Before I came to the market, the market was about 6,000 yuan.
The market was about 1,000 yuan.
Now, the market is about 6,000 yuan.
Shiyan is a city of Shanshi Province in central China.
It boasts the highest growing GDP in the country.
The city is one of the star performers fueling the nation's economic growth.
It was five years ago that Lin moved to Shiyan.
Not wanting to spend excessive money on living expenses, he rented an apartment for $90
a month.
He currently works at an IT company, performing server maintenance for websites.
He's achieved a stable income, but he states that he has no interest in working to move
up in the world.
Lin has his own way of interpreting the meaning of lying flat.
I was told to leave the city and leave the city.
The city is not just a remote area.
It's not like you're living a long life.
You can also live in the city.
I never had a home.
I was told to leave the city.
I'm not going to find him.
At the end of the year, when I was 12 or 9 years old, I met many people who gave me this gift.
I bought this gift with the size of my hand, where one was for adults and that was my first time.
When we started working, it was the last bus when we went to the market.
Which means we spent the next day running around 2000 to 300 yuan.
When he was 26, Lynn borrowed over $45,000 to start a company with 10 employees, providing financial consulting.
Just six months later, the government strengthened the restrictions on financial institutions.
Unable to scrape by under the new rules, his company went out of business.
Even as the economy of China grows, many young people like Lin are rewarded for their work only with exhaustion.
and the overall results of the company,
we all saw their high-end support.
So I would like to say that this thing will also be a lot of experience.
I hope that I will not be able to do anything
like, for example, you see, I am not Wang Si Chong.
If there is no support, there is no money
to do anything that can help change its own way.
It is not possible to do a very realistic look.
It can do such a look.
Although Lin remains firm and is decision to get by with the bare minimum, he worries just like anyone else.
I was a little bit more focused on them.
Sometimes I thought,
I would be like,
I feel like I'm not a real person.
I was like,
I think there's no such thing as a good solution.
There are certain reasons.
But you have to go to the cemetery to see what's going on.
To see what's going on.
Meanwhile, Sun continues taking care of his father as he lies flat.
But recently, he's made a change to his behavior.
It began as his father's health showed signs of decline,
spending more days in bed.
Even with his lifestyle, soon felt that he had a responsibility to uphold.
He hoped that earning even a little extra money might put his father at ease.
He was able to find a kind of work that didn't require money or experience.
Tofu making.
making. He and his father made the cooking pot for the project together.
It doesn't matter.
I don't want to buy a car.
This is not possible.
Do you want to drink?
Yes.
I want to drink.
How is it?
It's good.
The young people who have chosen to live flat are one product of the reality behind Chinese society.
on with life, their fears for the future rest always beside them.